<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John Mark Agosta&#39;s musings</title>
    <description>Occasional notes on current readings, theory, language &amp; (gasp) culture.
</description>
    <link>http://johnmarkagosta.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://johnmarkagosta.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 12:18:29 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 12:18:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>In High Tech -- what really really keeps women out.</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;gender-imbalance-in-hiring-in-silicon-valley&quot;&gt;Gender imbalance in Hiring in Silicon Valley&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This issue has risen to national attention, notably in the case of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/03/28/technology/ellen-pao-kleiner-perkins-case-decision.html?_r=0&quot;&gt;Ellen Pao&lt;/a&gt;, and, in entirely
different context, appearing today in NYT Sunday Review opinion piece, by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/10/11/opinion/sunday/what-really-keeps-women-out-of-tech.html?ref=opinion&quot;&gt;Eileen Pollack.&lt;/a&gt;
I can empathize with Ms. Pollack, sharing the same degree and Alma Mater, but offer a view into different circumstances.
Having gone through a hiring process this year as a data scientist, then soon after succeeding in finding myself a new manager attempting to hire, I offer
this anecdotal view from the front lines of hiring in the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make this tangible consider a typical sample of names from resumes that our corporate recruiters send us, scrambled for the sake of the candidates’ privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Misha&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semenovich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shima&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zare Borzeshi&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Syed Fahad&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mabroukeh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;YuanFeng&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhang&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jingyu&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Du&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tomas&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paunic&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ehsan&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ghassempour&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tianchuan&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wang&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shasikanth&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shau&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Corey&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bright&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Qiaona&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pessoa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Avishkar&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thampy&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vanja&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Singliar&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lucio&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hu&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do respect the work of our recruiters to find qualified candidates from all available sources in a fast-paced, viciously competitive job market.  The list is a typical mix of Asian, Eastern European, Middle Eastern and occasional South American talent, typically who came to the U.S. for graduate school, then stayed for employment in high tech.  Less than one in ten will have U.S. undergraduate degrees, and of those a small fraction will be U.S. born.  I find myself in most all cases not even knowing the the gender of the candidate when I select which resumes for interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eileen’s concern about a juvenile male oriented culture is familiar to us who share her background, but its just one of many expressions, and not uniform within tech. The culture is by nature of its origins a seat of multi-culturalism, and also&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What keeps women out of the larger, less visible expanse of high tech is determined by the gender imbalance in education in parts of the world for which we rely on the overwhelming large fraction
of our talent,  not what goes on in the traditional sciences in U.S. universities, nor in the hiring processes of our companies.  THe future has a bright side: the trends toward an expansion into “softer” tech - in complemenary fields of design, user experience, and linguistics promise to bring with
it a more gender balanced culture. It may not be the solution the critics seek,  but at the bottom, increasing the number of women in tech would best be achieved by improving their chances in their
countries of origin.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://johnmarkagosta.com/jekyll/update/2015/10/11/gender_blind_hiring.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://johnmarkagosta.com/jekyll/update/2015/10/11/gender_blind_hiring.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jumping the Airport Security Line</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-sign-up-for-tsa-pre-privileges&quot;&gt;How to sign up for TSA-Pre Privileges&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not well known that you can apply for a “Known Traveler Number” (KTN) from
Homeland Security’s TSA &lt;a href=&quot;https://universalenroll.dhs.gov&quot;&gt;Universal Enrollment Services&lt;/a&gt;
pre-approval program.
Enter the KTN when you make your reservation and your boarding pass will grant you
unfettered access to the &lt;em&gt;TSA-Pre&lt;/em&gt; line at airport security, so no
waiting on the long lines with everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not the well publicized commercial &lt;em&gt;ClearMe&lt;/em&gt; service whose kiosks
one sees outside security stations.  That runs $179/year. The TSA’s program
has a one-time $85 fee. &lt;em&gt;ClearMe&lt;/em&gt; has some additional advantages, such as
including family members up to 18 year’s old. You decide if it is worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sign up fill out the &lt;em&gt;Pre-Enroll&lt;/em&gt; instructions on the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://universalenroll.dhs.gov&quot;&gt;Universal Enroll&lt;/a&gt; website.
After you do, you’ll get a choice
of appointment times for an interview at a TSA-sponsored office typically near a
major airport.
In inscrutable
government fashion the site enjoins you, “&lt;em&gt;At this time, please only pre-enroll if
you will visit an enrollment center within the next 120 days.&lt;/em&gt;” I’m not sure
what this means. Should one fear
that applications may no longer be taken for grant of such
magnanimous privileges past 120 days from now?  Or that there’s a growing trend to
procrastinate among applicants to put off their appointments that the government
wants to put to an end? I just went and
signed up for the first appointment available. 
In San Jose, CA the office is run by &lt;em&gt;IdentoGO&lt;/em&gt;. It occupies a non-descript suite
in the back of a sign-less office building.  Thank goodness for Google Maps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you enter, an appropriately surly employee will have you sign-in with the time
that you’ve arrived, as given by a digital clock next to their clipboard. The employee
will then diligently highlight the time you’ve entered in yellow highlighter. Shortly
thereafter you will be led into a closed room where your passport will be scanned and
fingerprints taken and you will be prompted on a computer screen with exactly the same
questions that you filled out on the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However before the interview begins the interviewer, notable for her
excessive use of eye-makeup, will call the desk where you signed in
and verify your arrival time as was highlighted in yellow, to check
that your arrival time is not more than seven minutes past your
designated appointment time.  &lt;strong&gt;This is clearly the most stringent
requirement you need to meet to complete your application.&lt;/strong&gt;
Conceivably if you don’t meet this test your patience may be tested by being asked to wait
until a free appointment slot opens up, on a time-available basis, on the outside
chance that one would be available before close-of-business that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promptness on your part is valued, but not on the government’s part.  Once your
interview is complete, you’ll be given a receipt and informed that a decision will
be made on your application within 45 days, during which one imagines computers will be
running day-and-night to verify your street address, and so on.  Then with luck upon approval
one additional travel nuisance will be lightened if not eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 18:56:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://johnmarkagosta.com/uncommon/knowledge/2015/07/22/airport-security.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://johnmarkagosta.com/uncommon/knowledge/2015/07/22/airport-security.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>uncommon</category>
        
        <category>knowledge</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Excuse Me, Get Up!</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;learning-languages-by-using-them&quot;&gt;Learning languages by using them&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The natural way to pick up phrases in a new language is to try saying something and see what response one gets.  Think of how children learn.  It’s a kind of active learning—say something, often in imitation of something you’ve heard, then see what your interlocutor says in response, if it was anything like what you expect. An embarassing moment can be a powerful teacher.  Soon the sounds you make start taking on meaning. This way of learning is hardly what one would call &lt;em&gt;studying&lt;/em&gt; a language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this fashion, I make an advocation of asking foreign language speakers to repeat common phrases for me.  We’re blessed in high tech in the Bay Area, that English is the &lt;em&gt;lingua franca&lt;/em&gt; (ironic phrase aka, the ‘‘french’’) among a multi-lingual population for which English is a second (third, …) language. A native English speaker is among a minority—that’s grist for another time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;embarrassed&quot;&gt;Embarrassed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take this exclamation in Mandarin:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;不好意思  (Bù hǎoyìsi)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;meaning; “I’m embarrased to ask…”,  roughly, literally: 
&amp;gt; Not Yes! Meaning/Desire! Think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In context, this came about when my way was blocked along a bike path through a high-tech campus by a Chinese-speaking crowd having breakfast.  So I asked a young intern what should I say to excuse me which translates idiomatically to “Feel(ing) embarrassed” according to Google Translate.  The 1st 2nd &amp;amp; 4th idiograms are familiar from Japanese Kanji, roughly meaning No, Good (think &lt;em&gt;ii-desu&lt;/em&gt;, also the second character in Mandarin “Ni hao” - Hello.), and think (as to introduce an opinion).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;excuse-me&quot;&gt;Excuse me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Google’s translation with a grain of salt. For “excuse me”  Google-Translate specifically returns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;对不起！ (Duìbùqǐ!) At not (the) start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;get-up&quot;&gt;Get up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again the Japanese is helpful, where 起 means “get up”. (对, which works like a preposition in Mandarin, has no Kanji equivalent).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about 意, which she wasn’t sure has a Kanji equivalent?  It actually does, meaning “idea,” or “desire” as in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;意気地 (ikuji) “self respect” (Japanese)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second kanji “do” as in Aikido, meaning spirit, the last “chi” (ON reading), meaning 
“ground”. Mnemonic - Desire-(my)-Spirit-(to_be_)grounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The charm in this free association is that the conceptual connections, wrong or right, assist associating meaning with the symbols.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://johnmarkagosta.com/2015/07/07/excuse_me_get_up.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://johnmarkagosta.com/2015/07/07/excuse_me_get_up.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We built this blog on Jekyll and GitHub</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;setting-up-static-websites-hosted-by-github-with-jekyll&quot;&gt;Setting up static websites hosted by &lt;em&gt;Github&lt;/em&gt;, with &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes that’s a mouth-full, but it describes the shortest path to setting up a blog for the modestly code-savvy blogger.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://http://jekyllrb.com/docs&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is the simplest of all content management systems for building a website.
Github, if you are familiar with it as a code-sharing repository, incidentally also serves webpages. Think of
the &lt;code&gt;README.md&lt;/code&gt; file that &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; shows for each respository. So as a sideline, they’ve created a way for one to serve a directory with collections of pages residing in a repository.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In its own words, &lt;em&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware, static site generator.&lt;/em&gt;  This means one can run it to
creates a website.  To create page content, place files in a designated folder in &lt;em&gt;Jekyll’s&lt;/em&gt; directory structure.
These files can be conventional html  files, perhaps left over from a previous website, or, more
conveniently, files written with &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/markdown-basics/&quot;&gt;markdown&lt;/a&gt; that it styles and converts to html, with templates for custom
formats such as headers and footers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; is a command line application which includes a web server that is written in &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt;.  To run &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt;,
&lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; must be installed on one’s local machine, then the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; package (a &lt;em&gt;Ruby gem&lt;/em&gt;) installed for &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt;.
Then to expose the website publically, push the
&lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; directory structure to a &lt;em&gt;Github&lt;/em&gt; account created for that purpose and it’s complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BTW, there is a &lt;em&gt;python&lt;/em&gt; work-alike to &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; called &lt;em&gt;Hyde&lt;/em&gt;. Be cautious about getting involved with this evil twin! As pythonic as one may be, the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; installation is straightforward, and you’ll end up learning about &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; which is a really cool language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/categories/github-pages-basics/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/em&gt; documentation&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, one can create a
markdown-editable site entirely with &lt;em&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/em&gt;, but it will lack any &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt;’s templating  nicenesses.  We won’t go there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-steps-to-get-this-in-place&quot;&gt;The steps to get this in place&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;set-up-jekyll-in-ruby&quot;&gt;Set up Jekyll in Ruby&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Install &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; on your machine, if it’s not already there. The current version is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;~$ ruby –version&lt;br /&gt;
ruby 2.2.2p95 […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll also need &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt;’s package manager, &lt;em&gt;Bundler&lt;/em&gt;.  &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; comes with a built-in package manager called &lt;code&gt;gem&lt;/code&gt; that manages &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; packages that are called, naturally,  &lt;em&gt;gems&lt;/em&gt;.  &lt;em&gt;Bundler&lt;/em&gt;  is used to run &lt;em&gt;Ruby&lt;/em&gt; in an environment that guarantees that the needed packages are loaded and up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create the &lt;code&gt;Gemsfile&lt;/code&gt; that &lt;em&gt;Bundler&lt;/em&gt; uses to set the environment; &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/github-pages/&quot;&gt;see the GitHub suggestion&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Run&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ bundle install&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to implement that gems file in the directory where the Gemsfile resides, typically just below your repository directory. 
The trick is that this directory must be both a git repository and a &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; site.  I did this by first creating the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; site, then creating the repository and copying the site’s contents into the repository.  &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; will complain if you create a new site within an existing directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, first the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; setup:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a Jekyll site, in a temporary dir.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ bundle exec jekyll new my_tmp_site&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can try it out the site by building it, then running the local server to inspect it’s pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ bundle exec jekyll build my_tmp_site&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connect to the directory and start the server&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ cd my_tmp_site; jekyll serve&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should respond with a message that you can browse the site, at &lt;code&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;OK, cntl-C out of it (killing the server) and go to &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; to  create the blog’s repository.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;create-a-user-page-repository&quot;&gt;Create a user page repository&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create an account on &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com&quot;&gt;github.com&lt;/a&gt; if you don’t already have one. Otherwise create a new repository &lt;strong&gt;whose name must be “your-github-account”.github.io&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll create a &lt;em&gt;user page&lt;/em&gt; repository assuming the repository you are creating is solely for hosting your blog, not as part of a documentation site for a code project. You can choose the README option, and optionally choose a license file.  (Or go to e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativecommons.org&quot;&gt;creativecommons&lt;/a&gt; and choose an appropriate license.)  &lt;em&gt;Don’t go into settings and choose the auto-generated option!&lt;/em&gt;  That’s for a GitHub website that doesn’t use &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt;.  When &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; sees the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; directory structure in your master branch, &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; knows to run your contents through the &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; templating engine and serve your site! 
To be exact, &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; knows this because the repository name is the same as your account name, eg.   &lt;code&gt;jmagosta.github.io/jmagosta.github.io&lt;/code&gt; to generate a  website from the Jekyll site at http://jmagosta.github.io.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content from the master branch of your repository will be used to build and publish your &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To combine the repository and site directories, clone the repository&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ git clone http://github.com/jmagosta/jmagosta.git&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then &lt;code&gt;mv&lt;/code&gt; the entire contents of &lt;code&gt;my_tmp_site&lt;/code&gt; to the root of the repository. (Note that the &lt;code&gt;Gemfile&lt;/code&gt; stays at the level below, where you’ve been running &lt;em&gt;Bundle&lt;/em&gt; commands. )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then all that’s needed is to commit and push the site contents to the new remote repository:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;$ git add .&lt;br /&gt;
$ git commit -m”new Jekyll build”&lt;br /&gt;
$ git push origin master&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-edit-run-deploy-cycle&quot;&gt;The edit, run, deploy cycle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since &lt;em&gt;Jekyll&lt;/em&gt; serves locally, and also identically on the &lt;em&gt;GItHub&lt;/em&gt; server, you can see you changes locally simply by keeping the local server running as you edit markdown files in your repository.  Edits will appear as you refresh your browser pointing to &lt;code&gt;localhost:4000&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then when you want to deploy your changes, just push the repository commits to &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt;, so &lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt; will see them.  That’s all need be done to make the changes go ‘‘live.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://johnmarkagosta.com/2015/07/03/jekyll_via_github.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://johnmarkagosta.com/2015/07/03/jekyll_via_github.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
